<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entries>
  <entry id="deforestation_drivers" value="" editor-value="Smallholder Agriculture - particularly cacao, but also rubber and palm oil&#10;Forestry&#10;Fuelwood harvesting&#10;Mining" native-value="" native-editor-value="" citation="FPCF ER-PIN" citation-url="https://www.forestcarbonpartnership.org/sites/fcp/files/2015/September/Cote%20d'Ivoire%20ERPIN%20EN%20FINAL.pdf" citation-anchor="" status="citation-unconfirmed" comments=""/>
<paired-data id="representative_1"><entry id="representative_1.first_name" value="" editor-value="Dagobert" native-value="" native-editor-value="" citation="GCF Secretariat" citation-url="http://www.gcftaskforce.org/contacts" citation-anchor="" status="citation-unconfirmed" comments=""/><entry id="representative_1.last_name" value="" editor-value="Banzio" native-value="" native-editor-value="" citation="GCF Secretariat" citation-url="http://www.gcftaskforce.org/contacts" citation-anchor="" status="citation-unconfirmed" comments=""/></paired-data><paired-data id="redd_program_progress_1"><entry id="redd_program_progress_1.description" value="" editor-value="&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Law of Environmental Protection of the State of Tabasco&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This law aims to regulate all types of activities to protect the environment from the establishment and application of environmental policy instruments, as well as those necessary when it has been damaged. It also contains a chapter on climate change, within which the policies of the REDD + strategy can be harmonized. Article 28 states that state policy on climate change must promote adaptation and mitigation actions to global warming, where the principles of sustainable development are considered to contribute to reducing the risk of the population, their heritage and the conservation of resources Natural&lt;/p&gt;" native-value="" native-editor-value="" citation="" citation-url="" citation-anchor="" status="default" comments=""/></paired-data><paired-data id="redd_program_progress_0"><entry id="redd_program_progress_0.description" value="" editor-value="&lt;div&gt;State Program of Action on Climate Change (PEACC)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The implementation of the PEACC seeks to define, analyze and propose the strategic measures necessary to address climate change in Tabasco with mitigation measures (reduction of greenhouse gas emissions Greenhouse), and adaptation measures to ensure the integrity of communities and develop capacities to address adverse impacts. As a result, PEACC is an instrument to support public policies and actions related to climate change within the state government's sphere of competence, as well as to form an important element of the critical path for climate change policy in Mexico and Identify actions and measures to reduce vulnerability to the impacts of climate change and greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions. Concurring the EEREDD + is proposed as a state planning instrument where scenarios of emissions reduction by deforestation and forest degradation are identified, promoting actions that create favorable conditions to reach the goals.&lt;/p&gt;" native-value="" native-editor-value="" citation="" citation-url="" citation-anchor="" status="default" comments=""/></paired-data><paired-data id="institutional_framework"><entry id="institutional_framework.state_province" value="" editor-value="&lt;p&gt;Tabasco since 2011 has had an intersectoral committee on climate change. &amp;#160;This working group will help develop the &amp;#160;state REDD + strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tabasco is in the process of creating a REDD + Working Group (GT REDD+) which would be convened with CONAFOR, together with SERNAPAM. &amp;#160;It is envisioned the GT REDD+ will create the CTC-REDD + (technical advisory committee of REDD +), made up of experts (civil society, academia, private sector, NGOs) in the various Components of REDD + in the State of Tabasco. This committee will be responsible for providing useful and up-to-date information for decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;" native-value="" native-editor-value="" citation="" citation-url="" citation-anchor="" status="default" comments=""/></paired-data></entries>
